葛瑞芬，葛瑞芬
Griffin. Griffin.
- 葛瑞芬，我讲过了  - 我玩到一半
- Griffin, what did I say? - I'm in the middle of a game.
你要吃晕车药才能在车上玩游戏
You can't play that in the car unless you take your Dramamine.
现在吃也太晚了，我们快到了
It's too late for Dramamine. We're practically there.
别对我翻白眼
Don't roll your eyes at me.
你希望他又吐在车上吗？
You want him puking in the car again?
- 我说对不起了  - 那不是你的错
- I said I was sorry. - No, it's not your fault.
很臭哎
That was smelly.
- 才没有！那是意外  - 没人怪你，宝贝
- Was not! It was only an accident. - Nobody's blaming you, honeybun.
本来就很臭
It was smelly.
我跟着导航
- I'm following the GPS.
超臭的
- It stinked.
看，她说在猫鹰街左转
Look, she says left on Kitty Hawk.
不，不，爸
No, no, Dad.
- 我不要住这里  - 哦，别这样
- There's no way we can live here. - Oh, come on.
你又还没看到房子
You haven't even seen the house yet.
- 这边有电缆线  - 没事
- There are power lines. - Relax.
我身体里开始长肿瘤了
- I can feel the tumors forming already.
没人会长肿瘤
- No one's getting tumors.
- 什么肿瘤？  - 开玩笑的
- What tumors? - It's a joke.
你这白痴
Dumbass.
是笑话，白痴！
- It's a joke, dumbass!
不要这样说，宝贝
- Don't say that, sweetie.
15米后掉头
- Make a U-turn in 50 feet.
什么？
- What?
- 你忘了转弯？  - 是的，夫人
- You missed the turn? - Yes, ma'am.
白痴，耶！
Dumbass. Whee!
来吧
Come on.
不错吧？
Nice, right?
嗯
Yeah.
挺舒服的
Cozy.
我觉得挺好的
I think it's nice.
我也觉得挺好的
I think it's nice, too.
小猪兽也这么想
Piggy-corn, too.
包温先生、太太
Mr. and Mrs. Bowen.
嗨，抱歉来晚了  我们忘了在猫鹰街那转弯
Hi. Sorry we're late. We missed that turn on Kitty Hawk.
对啊，现代科技嘛
Yeah, modern technology.
她直接跑进去看了
She's just gonna go right in, start checking it out.
这篮筐好棒
That hoop is cool.
这棵树也不错吧
Nice tree, huh?
这棵树的历史比这里所有的房子还久
That's been here longer than any of the houses.
爬树一定很好玩
Be fun to climb.
- 妈，有个厨房！  - 哦，哇
- Mom, there's a kitchen! - Oh, wow.
我去看我房间！
I'm gonna go see my bedroom!
慢慢来，上楼梯小心
Slow down, please, on the stairs.
防盗系统没问题
That security system works. The owner was a bit of a technophile,
屋主是技术控，什么线都拉好了
so this house is wired for whatever you might need.
墙上都有喇叭，每间房都能听音乐
You'll notice he put speakers in all of the walls,so you can hear music in every room...
连厕所都有
including the john.
这边过去是厨房
So, this is the kitchen through here.
- 你们要看看吗？  - 当然
- Do you wanna see this? - Sure.
你们有人要坐公共交通上班吗？
- Will either of you two be commuting to work?
我不用，我在家带小孩
- Not me. I'll be home with the kids.
- 艾米是很棒的作家  - 哦，艾瑞克！
- Amy is an amazing writer. - Oh, Eric!
- 是真的  - 别说了！
- She is. - Come on!
她只是谦虚，她真的很厉害
She's being very humble right now. She's very good.
我很努力，但很难抽出时间
I'm trying to be, but you know, it's just hard to find the time.
我懂，我也有两个小孩
I know, believe me, I have two of my own.
他们都上大学了，真高兴他们都走了
They're in college. I'm glad they're gone.
我是说我总算又能拥有自己的生活了
I mean, I'm getting my life back.
您说过您在哪高就，包温先生？
Where did you say that you worked, Mr. Bowen?
强鹿公司，在莫林那里
John Deere corporate, over in Moline.
那是家好公司
That's a wonderful company.
我们有辆驾驶式割草机  很耐用，我们很爱强鹿牌
We have a riding mower. It's lasted us for years. We love John Deere.
如果我没被裁员现在一定很高兴
Well, I'd be very flattered right now if I hadn't gotten laid off.
- 抱歉，我不知道  - 没关系
- I'm sorry. I didn't realize... - That's all right.
我们的割草机质量是不错，没事
They do have a quality... mower. It's fine.
真的，但…
They do, but...
他们要裁员，我就…
They were making some cutbacks, and I was...
嘿，艾瑞克，来看这个
Hey, Eric, come look at this.
我也想，亲爱的，但我正在尴尬地聊天
I'd love to, but I'm in the middle of a very awkward exchange with our realtor right now.
来看看
- Come see.
不好意思
- Is that all right?
- 请别离开  - 请便
- Don't go anywhere. - Please.
- 你看那边有一块空地  - 是哦
- Look, there's a field down there. - Oh, hey.
- 那是谁的地？  - 市政府的
- Whose property is that? - That's city property.
那边会很容易起火
That's a good place for a brushfire.
你得试着喜欢这间房子
You have to try to like this.
好，我会的
Okay. I'll try.
你们想去楼上看看吗？
Would you like to see the upstairs?
我要去
Yes, I would.
你要带我们看主卧房吗？
And this is a master that you're showing us?
没错
That's correct.
上面怎样，孩子们？
How is it up there, kiddo?
我比较喜欢我们家
I like our house better.
我们别无选择，宝贝
Well, that's not an option, honey.
那根本不是卧房，是阁楼
You can call that a bedroom, but really, it's an attic.
葛瑞芬可以睡那里
That can be where Griffin sleeps.
这里采光很好
This place has so much light.
对吧，艾瑞克？
Huh, Eric?
很不错
Very nice.
是啊
Yeah.
非常好
Very nice.
这间房子面对…
The house faces...
对，街道的这一侧比较安静
Yeah, it's a little bit quiet on this side of the street...
一个街口以外，人已经越来越多了
but just one block up, things are starting to fill up.
真好玩，对
It's funny. Yeah.
小猪兽？
Piggy-corn?
不，小猪兽不是我的宝宝
No, Piggy-corn's not my baby.
她只是玩偶
She's just a doll.
她一半是小猪，一半是独角兽，看？
She's half-pig and half-unicorn, see?
这边有一只角，呜呜
She has a little horn. Honk, honk.
你在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
没有人
No one.
妈，我们喜欢这间房子！
Mom, we like this house!
老天，这完全卡住了
Jesus, this is really stuck.
可能太潮湿了，上礼拜都在下雨
That's probably just moisture. It rained last week.
好吧，我不知道
Okay. Well, I don't know.
我们预算里的房子都是这样的
All the houses are like this in our price range.
这幢是最不烂的
And this is the least sucky one we've seen...
- 我觉得，也许…  - 也许？
- so I think, maybe... - Maybe?
这个区有很多银行抵押房
Okay, look. Foreclosures have hit this neighborhood really hard.
所以还是有议价空间
There's some wiggle room on the price.
空间有多大？
How much wiggle we talking?
廉价搬家
小心点啊！
Come on, man!
抱歉
Sorry.
真好
Perfect.
别这么沮丧，孩子，这是暂时的
Buck up, kiddo. It's temporary.
我们毁了你的人生
We've ruined your life.
太棒了
Good.
万岁！
Yay!
嗨
Hey, hey, hey.
行了
Come on.
你说你会丢掉它们的
You said you wanted to get rid of that stuff.
你开玩笑吧
What, are you kidding?
这是我的旧货  为葛瑞芬存的
This is my old bat bank. I'm saving it for Griff.
对
Yeah, right.
葛瑞芬，我们练练
Griff, let's play some catch. Here.
起来！
Hi-yo, Silver!
很好，包温队！
Yeah! Nice. Team Bowen!
艾瑞克，随他去
Eric, leave him be.
我们很好
Well, we're bonding.
我不觉得
I don't know that you are.
我扔给你球，好吗？
I'll throw you a ball, okay?
为什么？
Why?
好玩
'Cause it's fun.
我给你一个短高球，好吗？
I'll throw you a pop-up, okay?
你得接住
You gotta go for this one.
准备好没？
Okay, you ready?
你接到了
You got it.
是我的错
Well, that's my bad.
我没接住
I missed.
没事儿
That's okay.
我们再试，是我的错  我没扔好
We'll try again later. It was my fault. I threw it too hard.
接球吧？
Well, get the ball, will you, kiddo?
很好！
Good job!
我们可以踢足球
He can play soccer.
或象棋
Yeah. Or chess, Eric.
我要把它丢掉
I'm getting rid of this.
你见过棒球吗？
Have you seen the baseball?
妈妈
Mom! Mom! Mom!
树发出了噪音
The tree made a noise!
- 什么？  - 树在嗥叫
- What? - The tree growled!
葛瑞芬  这是一棵老树
Okay, look, Griff, Griff, Griff, Griff. It's an old tree.
老了就会裂
Okay? Things creak when they get old.
告诉我
Yeah, tell me about it.
就像爸爸
Right? Like Daddy.
我怎么能让你开心？
What can I do to make it better?
我不知道
I don't know.
何不就去看看你的新房间
You wanna go inside and check out your new room?
- 好吗？  - 好
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 我们丢掉它好吗？  - 我不知道
- All right. Can we get rid of this? - I don't know.
- 说好  - 好
- Say yes. - Yes.
妈妈老了也会裂
Mommies creak when they get old too.
如果坏人打破窗户怎么办？
What if the bad guys break in a window?
警报器会响
Then the alarm will still go off.
但如果坏人剪断电线呢？
But what if the bad guys cut the wires to the alarm?
电线在房子里
The wires are in the house.
如果坏人去发电厂剪电线呢？
But what if the bad guys go to the power plant and cut the wires there?
他们会触电然后死掉
They'll be electrocuted and then they'll be dead.
如果他们死掉了，就不会进屋了
And if they're dead, then they can't get in the house.
警报开了？
We armed yet?
快好了
Getting there.
也许可以考虑养只狗
Might wanna think about getting a dog or something.
不要！
No!
这边说要按密码再按“停留”键
Here, it says you have to input the security code, and then the Stay key.
哦，是吗，聪明鬼？
Oh, yeah, smart guy?
怎么搞的？
What was that?
我刚刚也被电到了
Same thing happened to me.
这不是很怪吗？又不是冬天
Isn't that weird? It's not even winter.
它们找到这房子，把它整个吃掉
And they found this house, and they ate it all up.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
在玩啊
Playing.
你要看我变魔术吗？
Do you wanna see a trick?
什么魔术？
What kind of trick?
不可能，你怎么做到的？
No way. How are you doing that?
你试试看
You try.
你看起来好好笑！
You look ridiculous!
糟糕
Shoot.
那是什么？
What is that?
我只是把耳环丢在洗衣机后面了
I just lost an earring behind the washing machine.
那是长号
That's a bummer, honey.
我去找
I'll go look for it.
那儿有个缝
There's a leak back there.
有个新家真好
Great. Welcome to owning a new home.
我得做点什么
I had to do something.
这真是个鬼地方
This place is, like, a complete shithole.
连购物中心都没有
There's not even any malls. Like, the malls are boarded up.
天  很惨
Oh, my God, that actually sounds really sad.
- 你爸爸找不到  - 差劲
- So, your dad can't find... - Dude.
这个20年代的平房  是个杀人现场
This 1920s bungalow was the site of a murder.
我喜欢那出戏
Oh, yeah, I love that show.
天，那人真奇怪
Oh, my God, that guy's a total freak.
对
I know.
我是卡利根伯克  我来打扫房间
I'm Carrigan Burke, and I'm here to clean house.
对，我喜欢他说
Oh, yeah. I love when he's, like... Okay, ready?
“房间干净了”
"This house is clean."
“干净了”
"Is clean."
你能关掉它吗？
Hey, hey, hey. Can you turn that down?
进来吗？
Come in?
孩子们要睡觉
Kids are going to sleep.
你好，萝伦
Hi, Lauren.
你好，包温太太
Hey, Mrs. Bowen.
谢谢，晚安
Thank you. Good night.
包温太太？
"Mrs. Bowen"?
孩子们，得睡觉了
All right, lovebugs. It's time for bed.
这么乱，能收拾一下吗，葛瑞芬？
Look at this mess. Can you clean this up, Griff?
门卡住了
The door's stuck.
真好！
Awesome!
我想里面有磁铁
- I think there are magnets in there.
他们不是磁铁，是我朋友
- They're not magnets. They're my friends.
谁是你朋友？
Who are your friends?
迷路的人
The lost people.
谁是迷路的人？
The lost people? Who are the lost people?
他们住在这里，但不喜欢这里  他们想回家
They live here. But they don't like it. They wanna go to their home.
宝贝，我们在家里
Sweetheart, we are home.
我们没迷路
We're not lost.
这是我们的暂时的家，好吗？
This is our home for a little while, okay?
好，妈妈
Okay, Mommy.
你确定？
You sure?
为什么我要睡在上面这里？
But why do I have to be up here?
因为这是屋子里最酷的房间
Because this is the coolest room in the house.
而你是屋子里最酷的小孩
And you are the coolest kid in the house.
但我讨厌这个天花板
But I don't like the ceiling.
别说傻话了，睡吧
Now you're just being silly. Come on.
谁是我的超人宝贝？
Who's my super boy?
妈
Mom.
怎么，你长大就不喜欢了？
I'm sorry, are you too big to say it now?
不是
No.
那谁是我的超人宝贝？
Then who's my super boy?
我是
I am.
对，就是你
Yeah, you are.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好好睡觉，好吗？
All right, get some sleep, okay?
夜灯！我要夜灯！
The night-light! Night-light!
对不起，对不起，这样可以吗？
Sorry, sorry, sorry. Okay, okay, okay?
好些了吗？
Is that better?
葛瑞芬，没什么好怕的
Griffin, there's nothing to be afraid of.
好吧
Okay.
晚安，小家伙
Good night, buddy.
晚安
Good night.
葛瑞芬在叫什么？
What was Griff freaking out about?
- 他要夜灯  - 哦？
- The night-light. - Yeah?
“我要夜灯！”不知道他怎么了
"The night-light, the night-light!" I don't know what it is with him.
是啊，我们小孩太多了
Yeah, well, we got too many kids.
没错，两个应该就够了
I know. I said we should have stopped at two.
小梅不是问题
Maddy's not the problem.
还不是而已
Not yet.
敬那些小混蛋
Here's to the little jerks.
要带他去看心理医生吗？
Do you think we should take him to a shrink?
不用，他很好
No. No. He's fine.
他不好，都怪我在购物中心把他搞丢过
He's not fine. It's because I lost him in that mall.
宝贝，那是三年前了
Baby. That was three years ago...
你比他还要恐慌
and you were more freaked out than he was.
有些小孩就是容易紧张啊
Some kids are just nervous, you know?
我弟弟也是一样
- My brother was the same way.
现在他一人住在拖车里
- Yeah, now he lives alone in a trailer park.
- 他不是一个人  - 他是！
- He doesn't live alone. - Yes, he does!
不是，他有20只鹦鹉吧
No, he's got, like, 20 cockatoos.
你根本不是在安慰我！
You are not making me feel better!
说不定你可以去当教练
Maybe you could coach.
去高中吗？
What, high school?
对呀，应该很不错，你会很开心
Yeah. It'd be something. I mean, you'd be happy.
对，我会饿死，我们都会
Yeah, I'd be hungry. We'd all be.
在高中当教练养不活一家人
Can't support a family coaching high school.
我应该回去工作
I should go back to work.
又来了？别这样，你不会想要的
Again with that? Come on. You don't wanna do that.
你要把我和这些小怪物丢在一起？
You're gonna leave me all alone with these monsters?
我要买新内裤了，你看
I need new underwear. Look at these.
超悲伤的
These are sad.
你的内裤悲伤？
Your underwear is sad?
对，我的内裤很悲伤
Yes, my underwear is sad.
但我的很开心，过来吧
Well, mine are very happy right now, so get over here.
我说真的
I'm serious.
你不能用以前的薪水来拒绝工作
You can't keep holding out for something at your old salary.
是你在拒绝我吧
I think you're holding out.
- 干嘛不让我去工作？  - 我没有
- Why can't I just look for something? - I'm not holding out.
因为我们说好我工作你写书的
Because we agreed I'd work so you could write your book.
我们说好的
That's what we agreed about.
我没有在写书
I'm not writing my book.
等小孩去上学你就会写了
You will, when the kids go back to school.
别推到小孩身上，问题在我
Don't put this on the kids. This is all me.
嘿，我会找到工作的，好吧？
Hey, I'm gonna find something, okay?
你要相信我
You gotta trust me.
我们明晚要去参加派对
We got that dinner party tomorrow night.
你最喜欢派对了，我会喝波本酒
You love parties. You can watch me drink bourbon.
派对一定很闷，我们又不认识这些人
It's gonna be such a drag. We don't even know those people.
但盖瑞认识，他说那家男人可能要雇人
But Gary knows them. He says the husband might be hiring.
是啊
Yeah.
可能我们要转运了，你没感觉到吗？
Maybe our luck is about to change. Aren't you feeling lucky?
我觉得在“往上”了
I think things are looking up.
你这个呆子！
You're such a dork!
我是呆子？我是呆子？
I'm a dork? I'm a dork?
你和你悲伤的内裤
You and your sad underwear.
脱掉裤子
Take your pants off.
是的，夫人
Yes, ma'am.
- 真的吗？  - 对，真的
- Really? - Yes, really.
- 哇  - 准备上场
- Wow. - Play ball.
太好了
All right.
- 爸！  - 什么？
- Dad! - Yes!
嘿，怎么了，小家伙？
Hey. What's up, buddy?
楼上有东西
There's something upstairs.
我觉得我房间有东西
I think there's something in my room.
我等等就过去
I'll be out there in a second.
好运到此为止
So much for my luck.
- 别动  - 好
- Don't move. - Okay.
我很快回来，想想淫贱的事
I'll be right back. Think dirty thoughts.
怎么了，伙计？在哪里？阁楼上吗？
What is it, buddy? Where is it? In the attic?
房子在晚上本来就会发出声音  这很正常，我保证
Houses make noises at night. It's normal, I promise.
我们旧家不会
Not our old house.
这倒是真的
Well, that's true.
你在哪边听到声音
Tell me where you heard it.
这些小丑是哪里来的？
Where did all of these clowns come from?
我在那边找到的
I found them in there.
怎么有人会有一箱子小丑？
Why would somebody have a box of clowns?
人们有收集怪癖的，伙计
People collect weird things, pal.
我不喜欢这里
I don't like it up here.
怎么了？你害怕吗？怕什么？
What's the matter? You scared? What are you scared of?
全部都怕
Everything.
会好的，你要试着少担心一些，孩子
You're gonna get over that. You gotta try to worry less, kiddo.
懂吗？
You know?
如果你一直害怕，小梅也会怕
If you're scared all the time, Maddy's gonna get scared.
你要当好榜样
You gotta set a good example.
你是哥哥，要勇敢，知道吗？
You're the big brother. You gotta be brave, you know?
他妈的！
Holy shit!
怎么了？
What is it?
跟我说话
Talk to me.
你为什么徘徊不去？
Why do you linger here?
利用我，我能让你自由，利用我
Use me. I can release you. Use me.
怎么了？
What's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
艾瑞克，上面怎么了？
Eric, what is going on up there?
怎么回事？
What, what, what?
家里有只松鼠
We have a squirrel.
你真是个疯子！
You are such a nut ball!
- 尾巴又大又蓬！  - 吓坏我们了！
- Big, fluffy tail! - You scared us!
吓死人了！
Terrifying!
有啮齿动物，太棒了
Perfect. Rodents.
我明天会设陷阱
I'll set a trap tomorrow.
你抓到它以后会放回森林吗？
After you catch it with the trap, will you release it to the woods?
当然，这样你会比较开心吗，亲爱的？
Yeah, sure. Would that make you feel better, honey?
没抓到它之前我不要睡在上面
I'm not sleeping up there until it's gone.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
你是好人吗？
Are you nice?
你怎么去那里的？
How did you get there?
你哭了吗？
Did you cry?
怎么帮你？
Help you how?
但我看不到你
But I can't see you.
你旁边还有谁？
Who else is there with you?
葛瑞芬也可以来吗？
Can Griffin come, too?
是的，我会很勇敢
Yes, I can be brave.
我要先问妈妈
I have to ask my mommy.
不
No.
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
好
Yes.
但你们要怎么过来？
But, how will you get here?
小梅，你在干嘛？
Maddy, what's going on?
他们要来了
They're coming.
谁？
Who is?
谁要来？
Who is coming?
小梅！
Maddy!
快离开电视机前面！
Get away from the TV!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
他们来了
They're here.
网站上说可能是电路板的导线松了
It says here it's probably just a loose conductor in the electrical panel.
我要找电工
I'm calling an electrician.
干嘛付钱给别人？我来就行
Are you gonna pay him for what I can do myself?
他们收天价，葛瑞芬帮我就好，对吧？
Those guys charge an arm and a leg. Griff will help. Right, buddy?
- 葛瑞芬会帮你修电板？  - 对
- Griff will help you fix an electrical panel? - Yeah.
还有，我找到松鼠进来的地方了
I found out where the squirrel got in, by the way.
屋顶有个洞，我会堵住
There's a hole by the roof line. I'm gonna block it up.
爸爸，我不要吃麦片，我想吃比萨
Daddy, I don't want cereal. I want pizza.
早餐就吃？
- Yeah, for breakfast?
每餐都要吃！
- For all the time!
一天三次？
Three times a day?
葛瑞芬！我叫你别动我的手机！
Griffin! I told you not to touch my phone!
我没碰你的手机
I didn't touch your phone.
- 那它怎么烧坏了？  - 我怎么知道
- Then why is it fried? - How should I know?
又开始了
Here we go.
- 我要新手机  - 是吗？
- I need a new phone. - You do?
没手机了，亲爱的
No more phones, honey.
那不是奢侈品，爸爸，是必需品
This isn't a luxury item, Dad. It's a necessity.
要是你紧急要联络我怎么办？
What if you need to reach me in an emergency?
我们买不起，宝贝
We can't afford it, honey.
狗屁
That's bullshit.
你为什么这么自私？
What are you being so selfish about?
狗屁！
That's bullshit!
你想买新手机就要去打工
If you want a new phone, you could get a part-time job.
你找到工作我就会去工作
I'll get a job when you get a job.
嘿，她有工作！
Hey, she has a job!
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你们就是她的工作！
You kids are her job!
对，而且我做得很糟
Yeah. Which I apparently suck at.
我不这么想
I don't think you suck at it.
谢谢你，亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
嘿，小梅
Hey, Maddy.
你记得昨晚的事吗？
Do you remember last night?
你说“他们来了”
When you said, "They're here"?
那是什么意思？
What did you mean?
谁来了？
Who's here?
我朋友而已
Just my friends.
是吗？
Yeah?
你的想象朋友？
Your pretend friends?
不是，是迷路的人，不是想象的，妈妈
No, they're lost people. They're not pretend, Mommy.
那女孩真会给我找麻烦，天啊
That girl's gonna put me in a hole, man.
她被禁足了
She's grounded.
包温法官决定了，至少禁足24小时
Judge Bowen has spoken. For at least 24 hours.
提醒她今晚要照顾你们，好吗？
Remind her she's babysitting tonight, will you?
我讨厌肯洁照顾我们
I hate when Kendra babysits.
她也是，伙计
So does she, pal.
我最好弄陷阱抓松鼠
I think I might get some squirrel traps.
对，好主意
Yeah, that's a good idea.
这是什么？
What is this?
- 葛瑞芬，放下  - 什么？
- Griffin, put that down. - What is that?
- 放下来  - 那是骨头吗？
- Put that down. - Is that a bone or something?
- 对，放下来  - 我看看
- Yeah, just put that down. - Let me see.
应该是埋在这里的宠物或是马
I guess this is a buried pet or something. Maybe it's a horse.
说不定是一只猪！
Maybe it's a pig, too! A pig!
你吓到了吗？
Is this freaking you out?
- 别这样！别这样！  - 怎么了？
- Stop! Stop! - What's the matter?
够了，放回去
All right, put that back.
- 刷不过  - 抱歉
- That's not going through. - I'm sorry about that.
我太太说要取消几张用不到的卡
My wife said she might cancel one of the cards because we don't need them all.
没想到真取消了
- I didn't know she did it.
这张不是取消，是刷爆了
- It's not canceled, it's over the limit.
- 上面这么说吗？  - 对
- Is that what it says there? - Yep.
好吧，试试这张
Okay, let's try this one.
围裙很漂亮，你有参加工会吗？
Nice apron. Are you in the union?
这里的退休金不错吧？
You have a good pension here, for this?
- 抱歉  - 怎么了？
- Sorry. - Yeah?
这张也“取消”了
This one's "canceled" too.
两好球了啊，好吧
Strike two, huh? All right.
嘿，坏事不过三
Hey, third one's the charm.
祝你好运
Fingers crossed.
怎么样？没问题了吧？
How are we doing? Are we good?
- 这声音我喜欢  - 没问题了
- I like that sound. - Yeah, you're good.
好
Okay.
西谷广场购物中心
该死！葛瑞芬！
Damn it! Griffin!
我要你把漫画拿到楼上去
I asked you to bring these comic books upstairs.
我正要拿
- I was just about to do it.
对，我差点摔断脖子
- Yeah, I almost broke my neck.
一定是因为你边走边玩游戏
Because you were walking and playing that game at the same time, I bet.
谢谢你提醒
Thank you.
小梅？
Maddy?
是你吗？
Is that you?
小梅？
Maddy?
小梅
Maddy.
这样不好玩
This isn't funny.
好，大家都到楼下来！
All right, everybody, come downstairs!
- 家庭会议  - 爸！爸！
- Family meeting. - Dad! Dad!
- 走吧！肯洁！  - 爸！我有事跟你说！
- Let's go! Kendra! - Dad! I have to tell you something!
- 外边的花怎么了？  - 我不知道
- What's going on with the flowers out there? - I don't know.
你买了比萨？我弄了鸡块
Did you get pizza?- I just made chicken nuggets.
没关系，一起吃
- That's okay. We'll have both.
- 比萨！  - 我的宝贝想吃比萨
- Pizza! - My baby wanted pizza.
放在一起就是鸡块比萨了
You put them together, you got chicken nugget pizza.
爸，刚刚发生了怪事！
Dad, the weirdest thing happened!
- 你干嘛朝我大叫，葛瑞芬？  - 葛瑞芬，小声一点
- Why are you screaming at me, Griffin? - Griffin, you got to tone it down.
- 怎么了？  - “怎么了”？我告诉你
- What? - "What?" Here's what.
- 是什么？  - 怎么样？
- What's that? - What do you think of that?
- 不会吧！  - 真的！
- No way! - Yeah, way!
- 还有什么吗？  - 别再烦我了
- You know what else? - Now get off my back.
- 谢谢，爸  - 好
- Thank you, Dad. - You got it.
- 爸！你知道吗？  - 你说
- Dad! And guess what? - Yeah.
- 那颗球滚过地板  - 什么？
- The ball rolled across the floor... - What? What?
- 撞进衣橱里  - 嘿，你看！
- knocked into the closet... - Hey, look at this!
我买了你想要的遥控直升机
I got you that AR drone you wanted.
- 很棒吧？  - 你没在听我说话！
- Look at that. Isn't that cool? - Dad, you aren't listening to me!
- 上面有摄像头  - 真的？
- It's got a camera on it. - It does?
干嘛呢？
- What are you doing?
你在干嘛，美女？
- What are you doing, cutie?
看啊，这是你喜欢的耳环
Look at that. These are the ones you liked.
今晚派对可以戴
You can wear them to the party tonight.
爸，我还没说完！
Dad, that's not all!
漫画书堆得像座塔！
Then this tower of comic books formed!
我转过来时全都摔到我脸上
When I turned around they blew back at my face!
- 哇  - 就像是凭空出现
- Wow. - They had just appeared out of nowhere...
真的？太夸张了！
Really? That's crazy!
- 这不好笑，爸！  - 太有趣了
- It's not funny, Dad! - Yeah, it's hilarious.
你哪来的钱？
How did you pay for this?
你猜呢？我偷来的，我去抢银行
How do you think? I stole it. Robbed a bank.
唉呀
Uh-oh.
唉呀，爸爸糟了！
Uh-oh, Daddy-O!
我们要把这些东西拿回去  你要把东西都退回去
We gotta bring this stuff back. You have to take it back.
- 妈，不要  - 要
- Mom, no. - Yes.
- 我不会去退货  - 爸！
- I'm not bringing anything back. - Dad!
- 葛瑞芬  - 我们应得的
- Griffin. - I think we deserve a treat.
为什么没人听我说？
Why doesn't anyone listen to me?
葛瑞芬！天啊！你整个下午都这样
Griffin! Gosh! It's been all afternoon with this.
我要给手机设定密码
Just so you know, I'm putting the passcode on my phone...
- 你就不能用了  - 别把他当敌人
- so you can't get to it. - Please don't antagonize him.
- 爸，我们一定要搬家  - 我们不搬！
- Dad, we have to move. - We're not moving!
- 别再说了！  - 艾米
- Now, quit it! - Amy...
我以为小梅才会这样
No, I expect this from Maddy...
我现在觉得他才是小宝宝
but I'm starting to think that he's the baby in the family.
- 给你，妈妈  - 真好
- Here you go, Mommy. - Perfect.
谢谢你，甜心
Thank you, sweetheart.
葛瑞芬，对不起
Griffin, I'm sorry.
这跟我想的不一样
That didn't go as I hoped.
比萨好吃吗？
How's the pizza?
- 不好吃  - 是吗？
- Not good. - No?
不好吃
No.
配鸡块一起吃看看
You got to try it with the nuggets.
这样比较好吃
It's a little better.
我真差劲  我叫自己的儿子小不点
I am an awful person. I called my own son a baby.
我妈叫我可比这更糟
Well, if it's any consolation, my mom called me a lot worse.
艾瑞克有点不对劲
There's something wrong with him, Eric.
不只是焦虑
It's not just the anxiety.
- 他很好  - 他不好
- He's fine. - He's not fine.
他在说离谱的事  还深信不疑
He is saying the craziest things and he believes them.
你想怎么样？  你想让我
All right, what do you want me to do? You want me to...
他会把他交给其他人
I'll take him to someone.
可能吗？这不现实
How? I mean, you keep spending money that we don't have.
你为什么这么做？
Why are you doing that?
我在
I mean, what do I got, the illusion of...
幻想？
Spending money?
我尽力了
I'm trying to... I'm doing the best I can.
我尽力给你们想要的
I wanna give you guys what you want. I'm trying to...
我知道
I know. I know. I know.
今天不是个好日子，对吧？
Look, look, look, look, it was a bad day, okay?
会好起来的
It'll get better.
- 我去准备  - 好
- I'm gonna go get ready. - Okay.
- 是风车！  - 爸爸！转圈圈！
- It's the windmill! - Daddy! Break my arm!
- 好  - 转圈圈！
- Okay. Okay. - Break my arm! Break my neck!
- 爸爸？  - 转圈！转圈！
- Dad? - Neck! Neck!
爸，松鼠跑进来怎么办？
Dad, what if the squirrel gets in?
我封住洞了，像铜墙铁壁
I sealed up the hole. It's tighter than Fort Knox up there.
爸爸再见
Bye-bye, Daddy.
- 那干嘛还设陷阱？  - 这样才万无一失
- Then why did you leave the trap? - Insurance. You can't be too safe.
松鼠很狡猾
Squirrels are wily.
- 别担心了  - 再见
- Don't worry about it. - Bye-bye.
- 设定警报，有事打电话  - 我会
- Set the alarm, call us if you need us. - I will.
- 用新手机打给你  - 对，就这样
- Call you on my new phone. - Yeah, you will.
- 好好听姐姐的话  - 妈妈再见
- Be good for your sister. - Bye, Mommy.
- 门要锁好！  - 再见，我们会锁门
- Lock the door! - Bye. We will. Bye.
我不要睡觉！
- I wanna stay up all night!
不行，梅蒂森
- No. Madison...
- 整晚不睡！  - 不行，上楼去
- Stay up all night! - No, go upstairs.
不要！
No!
好了，这样舒服吗？
All right. All snug?
等一下
Wait.
小猪兽说要亲亲
Piggy-corn said she wants more kisses.
她这么说？
She does?
亲几下？
How many?
她说三下
She says three.
- 三下？  - 三下
- Three? - Three.
真的吗？好吧
Sure? Okay.
一、二、三
One, two, three...
二十，九百
20. 900.
我睡不着
I can't fall asleep.
为什么？
Why not?
我觉得暴风雨要来了
I think there's a storm coming.
盖瑞说你们大学在同一个棒球队
Gary tells me you played ball together in college.
他说你打击很强
He said you had quite the swing.
3A级，我现在宝刀未老
Triple-A, but I still do swing with the best of them.
别想歪了，芭芭拉
Don't get any ideas, Barbara.
他可以去打大联盟，他只是谦虚
He could have played in the majors. He's being very modest.
其实我的肩膀不好，没办法
No, I... Bad shoulder, so it wasn't meant to be.
能怎么办呢？
What are you gonna do?
还好你有B计划
Lucky you had a plan B to fall back on.
穿西装打领带也很好
There's nothing wrong with a suit and tie.
我一直跟儿子说这样才能付房租
I keep telling my son, it pays the rent.
我也有西装和领带
It's a good thing I have a suit and a tie then.
如果你愿意，周一我就能穿上
I can put it on Monday morning if you like.
几点上班？九点？
What time do I start? Nine?
他们刚搬到柳镇
They just moved to Willow Point.
我哥在90年代时有间房子在那里
My brother had a house in that development back in the 90s.
因为墓园的事，我们从没去看过他
We'd never visit him because of the cemetery thing.
光想到我就打冷颤
The thought of it just gave me the willies.
什么墓园？
What "cemetery thing"?
那个开发区以前是墓园
Just that that development was built on a former cemetery.
- 对，但墓地都迁走了  - 对
- Yeah, but they moved it though. - Yeah.
开发商把坟墓都搬到伯斯顿公园
The developers relocated the whole thing to Broxton Park.
有81万平方米，好多年前的事了
200 acres. This was years ago.
不会吧！整座墓园都搬走？
You're kidding me! They moved the whole cemetery?
中介没告诉你们吗？
The realtor didn't mention it?
没有，他们完全没提到
No. Actually, they didn't mention it.
把尸体都搬走实在不是什么好事…
Isn't it like, you know, very uncool to move all those bodies and...
又不是远古部落的墓地之类的
Well, it's not like it was an ancient tribal burial ground.
嗯，我知道
Yeah, I know.
两处开车只要十分钟，亲友还是能去凭吊
It's just 10 minutes away. People can still visit loved ones.
而且是搬到好一点的区域
But now it's in a nicer neighborhood.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
呆子，闭嘴
没什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
救命！
Help!
拜托，救命！
Please, help!
肯洁！
Kendra!
小梅
Maddy.
我们麻烦大了
We're gonna get in big trouble.
葛瑞芬？
Griffin?
葛瑞芬！
Griffin!
我好怕！
I'm scared!
不要靠近衣柜
Just stay away from the closet.
不要离开我！
Don't leave me!
肯洁！
Kendra!
葛瑞芬，开门！
Griffin! Please open the door!
救命！
Please help! Please help me! Please!
开门！
Open the door!
怎么回事？
What the hell is that?
亲爱的，停车
Honey, stop...
停车
Stop the car.
谁来救救我！
Somebody!
- 葛瑞芬！  - 爸！救命！
- Griff! - Dad! Help!
葛瑞芬！
Griffin!
哦，我的天！宝贝你没事吗？
Oh, my God! Baby, are you all right?
- 妈，妈！  - 没事了，宝贝
- Mom, Mom! - Okay, baby.
到底发生什么事了？
What the hell is going on?
妈！
Mom!
爸，妈
- Dad, Mom...
- 怎么…  - 有声音
- What's going... There were voices,
我被关在地下室，树抓住葛瑞芬
I got locked in the basement and the tree grabbed Griffin...
慢慢讲，我不懂…你说什么？
- Slow down. I cannot... What did you say?
我找不到小梅了！
- I can't find Maddy!
梅蒂森！
Madison!
小梅，亲爱的
Maddy, honey...
梅蒂森！
Madison!
小梅？
Maddy?
妈妈
Mommy...
- 梅蒂森？  - 妈妈
- Madison? - Mommy...
妈妈
Mommy.
妈？
Mom?
妈！
Mom!
葛瑞芬，怎么…
Griff. What...
妈妈？妈妈？
Mommy? Mommy?
小梅，你在哪里？
Maddy, where are you?
妈妈，妈妈
Mommy. Mommy.
爸爸，是你吗？
Daddy, is that you?
- 我不懂怎么回事  - 但我们得报警
- I don't even know what happened. - I know, but we have to tell them.
我们要找出真相
We gotta figure out what happened.
我们不能报警
We can't call the cops.
你要告诉他们什么？我们的女儿…
What are you gonna tell them? That our daughter got...
- 我不知道怎么回事  - 我会说…
- I don't know what just happened. - I'm gonna tell them...
我们要先弄清楚状况，好吗？
We need to figure out what's going on. Okay?
听我说，听我说
Listen to me. Listen to me.
如果你报警
- If you call the cops
- 警察会怪我们  - 他们不会
they're gonna blame us. - No, they're not
- 他们不会相信  - 我们老实说
gonna blame us. We're just gonna tell them what happened.
- 到处都会有记者  - 说实话就好
We're just gonna tell them the truth.I'm gonna tell them the truth.
我要跟他们说实话
I'm gonna tell them the truth.
我们一起说实话
We're gonna tell them the truth together.
我要老实说，我要告诉他们
I'm gonna tell them the truth. What happened, I'm gonna tell them.
但我们不知道实话是什么，亲爱的
But we don't know what the truth is, honey.
艾瑞克，我们需要帮忙
Eric, we have to call somebody.
一定有人会相信我们
There's gotta be somebody who's gonna believe us.
超自然研究部
葛瑞芬最早发现事情不太对劲
Griffin was the first one to notice things.
有声音跟一些东西
Noises... and just things.
我们以为是他乱说
We thought he was making it up.
对不起，孩子
I'm sorry, buddy.
我们不知道还能找谁
We didn't know where else to go.
你来这里是对的
No, you did the right thing coming here.
我在这里念书的时候
When I was a student here
听过关于这个部门的疯狂传闻
this office had the craziest reputation.
我想现在还是一样
I think we still do.
请问你丈夫在哪里？
May I ask where your husband is?
他在家陪大女儿肯洁
He's at home with Kendra, our oldest.
我们不想让小梅一个人
We don't wanna leave Maddy alone.
上次和她接触是在她消失后吗？
The last time you had contact with her was after she disappeared?
只有一次，透过电视机
Just the one time, through the television set.
抱歉，我知道这听起来很不正常
I'm sorry... I hear how crazy this sounds.
我知道一定很可笑
I know I must sound ridiculous.
不会，一点也不疯狂
No, it doesn't. It doesn't sound crazy at all.
- 是我的错  - 不是的
- It's my fault. - No, it is not.
看着我，不是你的错
Look at me. It is not your fault.
你为什么觉得是你的错？
Why do you think it's your fault?
我把她一个人留在那里
I left her alone.
我知道我不应该那样
I knew I shouldn't have.
但我很害怕
But I was scared.
你当然会害怕
Of course you were scared.
你一定要把我妹妹救回来
You have to get my sister back.
你一定要
You have to.
你做得到吗？
Can you do that?
我会试试看
I can try.
就是那台电视
That's the TV...
小梅的手就压在那里
where Maddy's hands were pressed against.
葛瑞芬在这座楼梯第一次被树抓住
This is the staircase that Griffin was first grabbed by the tree.
可能和小梅的事有关
It's probably something to do with Maddy.
还有我们在这边会被电到
And then there's that. That's a little shocker.
你们想吃三明治吗？
You guys want some sandwiches or something?
- 不用了  - 我要开始录了
- It won't be necessary. - I'm gonna start recording.
- 可以吗？  - 可以
- Is that cool? - Yeah.
请便
Knock yourself out.
这是实心的墙
That's solid wall.
我又戳又敲的试过无数次了
I've poked and prodded about a hundred times, so...
但你们觉得她是从这边被拉走的？
But you think she got pulled through there somehow?
我们不知道
We don't know.
你们觉得这是某种神秘通道吗？
What do you think, it's like a magic portal?
我说了不知道
I just said we don't know.
这给我好吗？
Do you mind if I hold onto that?
她回来后可能会想要
Till she gets back.
我不希望混乱中弄丢了
I don't want it, you know, lost in the shuffle.
没问题
No problem.
我最近拍到很不可思议的事
I shot a pretty amazing occurrence recently.
在奈波维尔一间老房子的钢琴椅
We were at this old house in Naperville, and a piano bench...
在客厅移动了三米
rolled 10 feet across the parlor floor.
花了七小时的时间
It took seven hours.
- 移动三米？  - 对
- To roll 10 feet? - Yeah.
我用特殊缩时摄影机拍到的
I used a special time-lapse setting on my camera.
成功搞定
So, nailed the whole thing.
肉眼是捕捉不到这种事的，所以…
You can't catch that kind of a thing with the naked eye, so I...
你的缩时摄影机拍到了吗？
Did you get all that on your time-lapse camera?
根据我的经验
From my experience...
这应该不是典型的闹鬼
this doesn't seem to be a classic haunting.
你们的情况
What you have here...
应该比较接近恶灵入侵
is probably closer to a poltergeist intrusion.
有什么不一样？
What's the difference?
鬼魂通常是无害的幻影
Ghosts usually appear as harmless apparitions.
但是恶灵
Whereas poltergeists...
会吵闹、攻击人
They're noisy, they lash out...
他们很暴力，会移动物品
they're violent, they move objects.
会突然出现，突然消失
It comes, and then it can just as suddenly go away.
然后把小梅也带走？
And take Maddy with it?
- 你没事吧？  - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
怎么了？
What's going on?
我那时候应该在家的
I should've been... home.
- 我应该在家  - 别这样，好吗？
- I should've been home. - Don't do this, okay?
你现在不能崩溃
I can't lose you now.
如果我失去信心
If I say it's not gonna be okay...
你要告诉我“一定会没事，亲爱的”
you have to say, "Of course it is, sweetheart."
不然我们撑不过去的
Otherwise, we're not gonna get through this.
房子扫瞄完了，现在系统要联机
We've done a scan of the house, and now we're wiring into your system.
这样如果小梅再跟你们接触
So if Maddy tries to make contact again...
我们会比较了解情况
we'll have a better sense of what's going on...
也许能把她带回来
which may help us get her back.
可以吗？
Does that sound okay?
听起来很好，可以快一点吗？
That sounds great. Can we do it a little faster?
小心
Watch out.
我问你
Let me ask you something.
你爸爸
Your dad...
有一阵子没工作了吧？
he's been out of work a while, right?
我想是的
Yeah, I guess.
没关系，没有人是完美的
That's okay. Nobody's perfect.
我只是在想
I was just thinking about it.
如果他想在短时间里发财
If he really wanted to make some money quick...
恶灵绑架案好像不错
a poltergeist abduction isn't a bad idea.
就算最后是假的也没关系
Even if it turned out to be a fake.
只要公开以后就能上电视
You go public with it, you do some TV appearances.
- 还会有真人秀  - 你够了没？
- You get your own reality show. - Would you stop?
那不是很赞吗？
How cool would that be?
我们不想要真人秀
We don't want a reality show.
我们只要小梅回来
We just want Maddy back.
你很厉害，小孩
You're good, kid.
非常厉害
Very good.
你在衣柜后面也装了热传感器吗？
Did you set up the heat sensor in the back of the closet yet?
还没
No, not yet.
我不知道怎么固定这东西
I didn't know how to fasten that thing.
用螺丝固定，伯伊
Screw it, Boyd.
好的
Okay...
老大
Captain.
“用螺丝固定”
"Screw it."
不会吧
Gotta be kidding me.
该死的
God damn it.
找到了
Gotcha.
无线温度计
不要！
No!
楼上都弄好了吗？
You all done up there?
好了
Yeah.
热传感器装在衣柜里了吗？
The heat sensor is in the closet?
算是
Sort of.
伯伊，你认真一点可以吗？
Boyd, I really need you to take this more seriously, okay?
可以吗？
Okay?
- 好  - 很好
- Okay. - Okay, good.
我的意思是
I think what I was saying is...
有些人相信现实分成很多层
some people believe there are different levels of reality.
我们在实体面
We're on a physical plane...
但死亡后，精神会到另一个层面
but when we die our spirits go to another level.
所谓天界或是灵界
An astral plane or a spiritual plane.
像是同时在这里却又不在这里
Which is sort of here and not here at the same time.
这样说吧
Okay...
看这边
Look at this.
好，然后这个
Okay. Now this...
谢谢你，珀威尔博士
Thank you, Dr. Powell.
我们在这个物理层
This is us here. In the physical level.
但小梅却被拉到这边
And somehow Maddy got pulled here.
在这里，却又不在这里
Here and not here at the same time.
正是如此
Exactly.
得有人去那里告诉她怎么回来
Then someone should go in there and show her the way back here.
这是个好主意
That's actually not a bad idea.
我敢肯定…
I'm fairly certain...
我们听不见她，但她能听见我们
Maddy is able to hear us a lot better than we can hear her.
所以这个设备可以过滤干扰
So this equipment is going to filter out all the interference...
让我们比较能和她沟通
so that we'll be better able to communicate with her.
我们要怎么开始？
How do we start?
只要叫她就好
You just call out to her.
好
Okay.
小梅？
Maddy?
梅蒂森，我是妈妈
Madison, it's Mommy.
你听得见吗？
Can you hear me?
梅蒂森，我们要跟你说话
Madison, we wanna talk to you.
你要让我们知道你很安全
We just want you to let us know that you're safe.
你在这里吗？
Are you with us?
小梅，我们要听见你的声音  好吗，亲爱的？
Maddy, we need to hear your voice, okay, sweetheart?
你跟妈妈打招呼好不好？
Can you say hello to Mommy?
你在这里吗？
Are you with us?
我们都好想你
We all miss you so much.
妈妈真的好想好想你
Mommy misses you so, so, so, so, so, so much.
嗨，妈妈
Hi, Mommy.
嗨，宝贝！
Hi, baby!
嘿，亲爱的，爸爸也在
Hey, honey. Daddy's here, too.
我们都在等你，亲爱的
We're all waiting for you, honey.
爸爸，你在哪里？
Daddy, where are you?
我们在家，你要回来我们这里，亲爱的
We're home. We need you to come back to us now, honey.
我试过了，可是我找不到你们
I tried, but I can't find you.
好，你要继续试，知道吗？
Okay, okay, okay. Keep on trying, okay?
因为我们就在这里，你快到了！
Because we are right here. You're so close!
妈妈？妈妈？
Mommy? Mommy?
爸爸，是你吗？
Daddy, is that you?
爸爸在这里，亲爱的
No, Daddy's right here, honey.
有人在她旁边！谁在那边，宝贝？
There's somebody with her! Who's with you, baby?
- 爸爸在这  - 谁在你旁边？
- Daddy's right here. - Who is with you?
他们都在我旁边
They're all around me.
小梅！小梅？小梅？
Maddy! Maddy? Maddy?
- 小梅，你听得见吗？  - 怎么了？
- Maddy, can you hear us? - What's going on?
妈妈，妈妈
Mommy. Mommy.
爸爸？
Daddy?
小梅！
Maddy!
梅蒂森？
Madison?
爸爸，我好怕
Daddy, I'm scared.
小梅！
Maddy!
等一下！
No, wait!
包温先生，不！
Mr. Bowen, no!
小梅
Maddy.
小梅，是我，亲爱的
Maddy, it's me, honey.
把她还给我！把她还给我！
Give her back! Give her back!
把她还来！你们不能抓走她！
Give her back! You can't have her!
出去！
Get out!
你没事吧？有被打到吗？
You okay? Did you get hit?
没有？你还好吗？
No? You okay?
都没事吧？
Everything okay?
那是什么？
What is that?
你没事，艾瑞克！
You're okay. Eric!
艾瑞克
Eric.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
包温先生，那里…
That, Mr. Bowen...
就是能带回小梅的地方
that's Maddy's way out.
但我们需要协助才能找到她
But I think we're gonna need some help in getting her there.
哪一种协助？
What kind of help?
你听过卡利根伯克吗？
Have you ever heard of Carrigan Burke?
不会是他吧
No effing way.
你的手怎么了？
What happened to your hand?
97年在密歇根州布兰查德
Blanchard, Michigan. '97.
屋顶储藏室闹鬼，灵魂不愿离开
Haunted root cellar. Spirit didn't wanna leave.
还好他们不是全部都很凶
Luckily, they're not all that angry.
我们的很凶
Ours is.
- 小子，还好吗？  - 没事
- Buddy, you okay? - Yeah.
他来了
Guy's here.
你们一定是包温夫妇
You must be the Bowens.
你一定是那位大师了
And you must be the cavalry.
珀威尔博士
Dr. Powell.
我们都准备好了，随时可开始
We're all set up if you wanna get started.
你好
Hey.
你是我的偶像，我是伯伊，幸会
Big fan. My name's Boyd. Nice to meet you.
拿着
Here.
他知道我们不上电视吧？
He knows this can't be on TV, right?
我告诉过他了
No, I told him that.
那他为什么还愿意来？
So why is he doing it?
那就是阴阳交界处？
This was the area of bilocation?
那边掉出一张桌子
A table fell out of there.
我差点被压扁
I was almost crushed.
情况还好吗？
Is everything all right?
还好的话就不需要我了
If it was, I wouldn't be here.
这间房子不干净
This house is not clean.
什么？
What?
好，重要的事先处理
All right, first things first.
告诉我小梅的一些事
I want you to tell me a little bit about Maddy.
你们会觉得她比较奇怪吗？
Did you ever feel that she was a little bit off?
- 奇怪？  - 对
- Off? - Yeah.
- 什么意思？  - 怎么样算是奇怪？
- What do you mean? - How do you mean, "Off"?
你听过她和不存在的东西说话吗？
Did you ever hear her talking to things that weren't there?
对，她有想象朋友，那很正常
Yeah, she has imaginary friends, but that's normal.
我想他是说小梅可能有这种天赋
I think what he's trying to say is that Maddy might have been born with a gift.
我不会说是“天赋”，但没关系
That's not the word I'd use, but all right.
你是说她能和鬼说话？
You mean she can talk to ghosts?
她才六岁
She's six years old.
代表她的生命力还很纯净
Which means that her life force is at its purest...
不会批判或是愤世嫉俗
without judgment or cynicism.
不然他们当初怎么会找上她？
Why do you think they reached out to her in the first place?
他们可没找你们其他人
They didn't reach out to any of you.
你一直说“他们”，他们是谁？
You keep saying "they." Who are "they"?
布鲁克告诉我这里以前是墓园
Brooke tells me that this development was built on a cemetery.
- 是吗？  - 爸，真的？
- Right? - Dad, really?
冷静点，是以前的事了
Calm down. It's a former cemetery. Former.
他们很早就把尸体移走了
They moved the bodies a long time ago.
- 他们…  - 把尸体搬到更好的地方
- They relocated... - They moved them to a nicer neighborhood.
我想他们没有
I don't think that they are.
我想他们只是告诉大家他们搬了
I think they just told people they moved the cemetery.
应该只是把墓碑移走吧
I think they just moved the headstones.
尸体都还在这里？
And they left the bodies?
哦，天哪
Oh, my God.
我们要应付的不只是几只恶鬼
This isn't just a few pissed off spirits that we're dealing with.
这跟我过去感应到的都不一样
This is unlike anything that I've ever felt before.
比较像是一群暴民
This is... It's more like a mob.
他们遭受了非常不公平的对待
They suffered a terrible injustice...
愤怒与沮丧形成一股强大的新力量
and that anger and frustration has created a new, more powerful force.
就是恶灵
The poltergeist.
他们被困住，绝望不已
They are trapped and they are desperate.
你女儿是他们脱离炼狱的门票
And your daughter is their ticket out of this purgatory.
他们想拿她怎么样？
What do they want with her?
他们要用她当作离开黑暗的灯笼
They want her to be their lantern in the darkness.
引领他们走向光亮
To lead them into the light.
如果她进入光亮会怎么样？
What happens if she goes into the light?
如果她走进去就没办法回来了
There's no getting her back if she does that.
他这么说并不表示…
Just because he said that, it doesn't mean...
那是真的，懂吗？
that's true, okay?
你说的每句话都不合理
Nothing you've said makes sense to me.
现在的每件事也都不合理啊
And everything else does, right?
衣柜、大树、天花板上闷烧的洞
The closet, the tree, the smoldering hole in the ceiling.
那些都很合理，只有我在鬼扯
All that makes sense to you, but I'm full of crap.
我不知道，可以吗？我不知道
I don't know, okay? I don't know.
我们只希望女儿回来
We just want our daughter back, okay? We just want our daughter back.
艾瑞克，我了解你的感受
Eric, I know exactly how you feel.
你怎么会了解？
I don't know if you do.
我这辈子每天都有这种感觉
I've felt it every single day of my entire life.
不知该相信什么，但你该相信
It is hard to know what to believe in, but I am here to help.
我是来帮忙你们的，对不？
You believe that, don't you?
好吧
Okay.
我们只能靠你了，动手吧
You're all I've got, so let's do it.
每个人都带着定位追踪器
Everybody gets a GPS tracker.
万一情况不对
This is gonna tell us where you are, anytime...
我们才能知道你们的位置
in case anything gets weird.
这要怎么弄？
What am I supposed to do with this?
放进口袋里就好
Just put it in your pocket.
很奇怪，对不对？
Weird, right?
是啊
Yeah.
他的腿怎么了？
What's with the leg?
我不知道
I don't know.
告诉我怎么操纵好吗？
Can you show me how to fly this thing?
好
Okay.
有点复杂，你要让我来吗？
It's kind of complicated. Do you want me to fly it?
我可以搞定
I can handle it.
你们可以问我，不必盯着我的腿
You gonna ask me about it, or just stare at my leg the whole day?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我们把话讲开吧
Let's just get this over with, shall we?
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
不，我们不想看，这太奇怪了
No, no, no. We don't need to see that. That's weird.
- 你怎么了？  - 你怎么了？
What happened to you?
2003年在葡萄牙
Portugal, 2003.
布萨科森林里的修道院
There was a monastery in the forest of Bussaco...
有一个很难搞的灵
with a particularly nasty entity.
你甩掉他了吗？
And you got rid of it?
他带着我的一块腿肉走的
Not before it took a piece of my leg with it.
好，谢谢你的分享，真恶心
Okay, thank you for that. That's gross.
我要去吐了，多谢
I'm gonna go throw up. Thanks.
那边又是怎么回事？
And what about that one?
这个故事很精彩
That's a good story.
这件事结束后我再告诉你，好吗？
Let's save that for after this is all over, shall we?
如果你没死的话
Assuming you don't die.
好
Okay.
- 你干嘛这样？  - 哪样？
- Why do you do that? - What?
说些当年勇的故事
You tell your old war stories...
好像你是个老家伙一样
and you make yourself sound like an old man.
干这行就是这样
Comes with the territory.
我们老得比别人快
We age in dog years.
你有小孩吗，伯克先生？
Do you have kids, Mr. Burke?
可惜没有
Sadly, no.
我太太觉得做这行不适合有小孩
My wife didn't think it was a good idea given our line of work.
不只是因为工作而已
It wasn't just the work.
- 你们两个以前…  - 很短暂
- The two of you were... - Briefly.
我们又年轻又傻
We were young and stupid.
只有一个人傻
Only one of us was stupid.
别自责了，我那时候真的很帅
Don't be so hard on yourself. I was irresistible back then.
我去检查楼上的数据
I'm gonna go check the readings upstairs.
她也是这样逃离我们的婚姻的
And she goes, just like she fled our marriage.
投入学术的怀抱，安全稳定的学术
Straight into the arms of academia. Safe, stable academia.
- 但还是很想我  - 我没有
- Still misses me though. - No, I don't.
你有，一点点
You do, a little.
一点都没有
No, not even a little bit.
她忘记我有感应能力
She forgets I can sense these things.
我有特殊能力，你知道的
I have special powers, you know.
也没那么特殊
They're not that special.
你还好吗？
You all right?
我有点害怕
I'm a little scared.
是哦
Yeah.
我也是
Me too.
我们要怎么办？
What are we gonna do about that?
我不知道
I don't know.
专心想小梅？
Think about Maddy?
试试看吧
Let's try that.
比较不害怕了吗？
Feeling less scared?
不，其实没有
No, not really.
嗯，我也没有
Yeah, me neither.
但我觉得比较有勇气了
I feel a little braver, though.
我也是
Me too.
我们好了
We're good.
布鲁克，开始录像！
Brooke, video's up!
- 走吧  - 我们这边都好了
- Let's go. - We're all set to go down here.
肯洁，把袋子里的皮带丢给我
Kendra, would you ever throw me that belt that's in that bag there?
好，我们先说清楚
All right, just so we're all clear.
第一，绳子是我们进出的桥梁
First, we use the rope to bridge the way in to the way out.
里面有一套不一样的规则
The rules are different in there.
没有上下之分
There is no up, there is no down...
也没有直线
and there are no straight lines.
所以我们要自己画一条
Which is why we have to make one.
这条绳子是我们的生命线
This rope is our lifeline.
如果我们放手就找不到回来的路
If we let go of it, we'll never find our way back.
成功了！
It worked!
等我们都弄好了
Once we've done that...
就派直升机去找小梅
we send the drone in to get eyes on Maddy.
稳住，要稳住了
Keep it steady, now. Keep it steady.
稳住直升机，葛瑞芬
Keep it steady there, Griffin.
是小梅！
Maddy!
小梅？
Maddy?
妈妈
Mommy.
妈妈？
Mommy?
小梅
Maddy.
妈妈？
Mommy?
是小梅吗？
Maddy?
- 梅蒂森，听到吗？  - 妈妈
- Madison, can you hear me? - Mommy.
梅蒂森！梅蒂森？
Madison! Madison?
梅蒂森，宝贝，小梅，甜心，我是妈妈
Madison, honey. Maddy, sweetheart, it's Mommy.
妈妈？
- Mommy?
小梅？
- Maddy?
爸爸？
Daddy?
梅蒂森！梅蒂森！
Madison! Madison!
- 放手！让我进去  - 听我说，艾瑞克
- No! I'm going in. - Listen to me, Eric.
- 我是妈妈，一定要去  - 妈，不行！
- I am her mother. I have to go. - Mom, you can't!
你不能进去！
You're not going in!
她太接近光了，我进去带她出来
She's too close to the light. I gotta go in and get her out.
不，我去，你去没用，她不跟陌生人走
No, I'm going. You can't go. She won't come to a stranger.
你没有经验
You've never done this before.
- 你不知道怎么应付  - 好，那我去！
- You have no idea what you're dealing with. - All right, I'm going!
葛瑞芬
家庭问题以后再解决，先带她出来
Sort all this out in family therapy. We've got to get her out of there.
大家别吵了！葛瑞芬到楼上了
Wait, everyone, stop! Griffin is already upstairs.
葛瑞芬！哦，我的天哪！葛瑞芬！
Griff! Oh, my God! Griff!
葛瑞芬！
Griffin!
我不应该留下她一个人的
I should have never left her alone.
不要！
No!
葛瑞芬！不要！
Griffin! No!
葛瑞芬！
Griffin!
不要！
No!
去楼下！抓住绳子！
Go downstairs! Grab ahold of the rope!
我发出信号你们就用力拉！
When I give you the signal, pull with all your might!
如果没用怎么办？
What if it doesn't work?
艾米
Amy.
亲爱的
Sweetheart...
会成功的
it's gonna work.
这不能失败！
This better work!
你说你能跟这些东西说话，对吗？
You said you could talk to these things, right?
告诉他们该放小梅回来了！
Tell them it's time to let Maddy go!
我全靠你了！
I'm counting on you!
这个小孩没有伤害你们
This child has done you no harm.
她也没有口出恶言
She speaks none harm.
等一下
Wait.
不，他离开画面了，找不到他了
No, no, no. He's off the screen. We lost him.
小梅？
Maddy?
葛瑞芬？
Griffin?
小梅，我们要离开这里
Maddy, we have to go.
我不能走
I can't.
你可以，我们现在就要走了
Yes, you can. We have to go now.
他们不会让我走的
They'll never let me leave.
那条绳子！
The rope!
绳子松掉了！
跑，小梅，快！
Run, Maddy, come on!
小梅！葛瑞芬！
Maddy! Griffin!
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
我抱住你们了，我的宝贝们  没事的，天啊
I got you, my babies. You'll be okay. Oh, my God.
他们还有脉搏
They have a pulse.
艾瑞克！
Eric!
他们在呼吸，她有呼吸
They're breathing. She's breathing.
妈妈在这里
Mommy's right here.
上帝！天啊！
Jesus! God!
他们没事吧？
Are they okay?
- 现在怎么办？  - 马上让他们泡水！
- What do we do? - Get them in the water now!
好，快点
Okay, come on.
快醒醒，宝贝
Wake up, baby.
好了，亲爱的
Okay, sweetheart.
快，宝贝，醒醒啊
Come on, baby, wake up.
听得见吗？听得见妈妈说话吗？
Can you hear me? Can you hear Momma?
好，快醒来，亲爱的
All right, wake up, sweetheart.
求求你
Come on.
葛瑞芬，求你快醒来
Griffin, please wake up. Please.
- 全靠你了，小家伙  - 快点醒来
- I'm counting on you, buddy. - I need you to wake up right now.
好孩子！好孩子！
Good boy! Good boy!
- 他醒了！  - 小梅还好吗？
- There he is! - Is Maddy okay?
- 小梅还好  - 小梅没事吧？
- Yeah, Maddy's okay. - Is Maddy okay?
小梅会没事的
Maddy's gonna be okay.
- 听得见妈妈的声音吗？  - 醒醒宝贝
- Can you hear Momma? - Come on, sweetheart.
求求你快醒来
Please wake up. Please wake up.
哦，亲爱的宝贝！哦，宝贝！
Oh, sweetheart! Oh, baby!
嗨，亲爱的，嗨，我的甜心
Hi, sweetheart. Hi, sweetheart.
嗨，妈妈，嗨，爸爸
Hi, Mommy. Hi, Daddy.
嗨
Hi.
嗨，甜心
Hi, sweetheart.
没事的，妈妈
It's okay, Mommy.
葛瑞芬救了我
Griffin saved me.
对，他救了你，知道为什么吗？
Yeah, he did. You know why?
因为你是我们的超人宝贝
Because you're our super boy.
对，没错
Yeah. Yeah.
我爱你们，我爱你，爸爸
I love you, two. I love you, Daddy.
哦，我的天，哦，我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
好了，快上车
All right, hop in your seat.
我们会回来吗？
Are we ever coming back?
不会，宝贝，打死都不会
No, sweetie. There's no way in hell.
好了，系上安全带
Okay, seatbelt.
嘿，谢谢你们
Hey, thanks for everything...
希望我们不会再见面
and I hope we never see you again.
不知道为何大家总是这么说
I don't know why they always say that.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
跟我说你欠我的那个故事
So tell me. I deserve it.
2012年在加州伯班克
Burbank, California, 2012.
拍摄闹鬼的洗车场那一集时
We were shooting an episode in a haunted car wash.
音效人员睡着了
And the sound guy fell asleep.
- 所以不是鬼？  - 不是
- So, not a ghost? - No.
只有拿着超大麦克风打磕睡的人
Just a dozy boom operator with a very, very large microphone.
说你的招牌台词
Do the line.
我不说
I'm not saying it.
妈，我要给萝伦看
Mom, it's for Lauren.
伯克，说一下吧！
Burke, give her the line!
这间房子干净了
The house is clean.
认真点，拜托
Better. Come on.
这间房子干净了
The house is clean.
哦，天哪！她会高兴死
Oh, my God! She's gonna freak.
“这间房子干净了”
"This house is clean."
其实没有
It isn't though.
当然干净了，亲爱的
Of course it is, sweetheart.
你帮那些灵魂进入光亮了
You helped the spirits go into the light.
但他们没有去
But they didn't.
- 爸，快走！  - 爸，快！
- Dad, go! - Dad, go!
他们没有进入光亮，妈妈
They didn't go into the light, Mommy.
他们要我带他们去，但我没进去
They needed me to take them but I wouldn't go in...
所以他们也没进去
so neither did they.
- 爸，走！  - 走！
- Dad, go! - Go!
快下车
Get out of the car.
亲爱的，你还好吗？
Honey, you okay?
你没事吧？
You okay?
- 大家都好吗？  - 好
- Is everybody okay? - Yeah.
艾瑞克，艾瑞克
Eric. Eric.
我在这里，宝贝，撑着
Here, baby. Hold on.
小梅呢？
Where's Maddy?
小梅呢？她在哪里？
Where is she? Where is she?
小梅！
Maddy!
妈妈
Mommy.
我觉得怪怪的，妈
Something's wrong, Mom.
小梅！
Maddy!
- 哦，天！  - 妈！
- Oh, God! - Mom!
小梅！
Maddy!
- 妈妈！妈妈！  - 小梅！
- Mom! Mom! - Maddy!
妈！
Mom!
- 抓紧！  - 妈妈！妈妈！
- Hold on! - Mom! Mom!
过来，宝贝，过来
Come on, baby. Come on.
妈妈！
Mommy!
加油，宝贝
Come on, baby.
撑住！
Hold on!
快拉！
Pull!
用力拉！
放过这家人
Release your hold on this family...
如同你们希望自己被释放
as you yourselves wish to be released...
不，别做傻事
No. Don't do something stupid.
我总是做傻事，所以你才离开是吧？
I always do something stupid. Isn't that why you left me?
卡利根，拜托
Carrigan, please.
他们不会放过这家人的
They're never gonna let this family go.
我不想在镜头前假装了，布鲁克
I'm tired of faking it for the cameras, Brooke.
你明知只有我能带他们进入光亮
I'm the only one left who can lead those souls into the light. You know that.
等一下！
Wait!
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
我知道，但我想这么做
I know. I want to.
等等
Wait.
我要怎么知道你回来了？
How will I know that you've made it back?
我会想出办法的
I'll think of something.
再见，布鲁克
Bye, Brooke.
艾米，过来这里
Amy, come here.
我们走
Let's go.
小梅！
Maddy!
我们快走！
Let's go! Come on.
小心头，走吧
- Watch your head. Let's go.
小梅，好，我们快走
- Maddy. Okay, let's go.
妈妈会抓住你
Mommy's gonna get you.
不要！
No!
肯洁！快过来，我们走！
Kendra! Come here. Let's go!
对不起，我对你那么坏，爸
I'm sorry I'm such a bitch to you, Dad.
没关系，亲爱的，之后再说吧？快走
It's okay, honey. Can we talk about it later? Let's go.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
嘿！
Hey!
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
这是我的工作！
- I've got a job to do!
等等！
- Wait!
爸！
Dad!
艾米，我们要找辆车
Amy, we gotta find a car.
艾瑞克，开我的车吧，快走
Eric, take mine. Go!
妈！
Mom!
快！我们走！
Come on! Let's go!
爸爸，它会跟着我们吗？
Dad, is it gonna follow us?
葛瑞芬，别向后看
Griff, don't look back. Don't look back.
有他的信号吗？
Any sign of him?
没有，定位抓不到他
Nothing. The GPS isn't picking him up.
目标：卡利根伯克  距离
等等，有信号了
Wait. We're getting something.
出售
- 你们好！  - 你好
- Hello! - Hi.
你们好！看来你们没迷路
Hello! You obviously found it okay.
胡帕中学棒球队
很漂亮，不是吗？
Isn't it beautiful?
我想就是这间了，学区好
I think this one is it. Great school district...
离高中球场也很近
the high school ball field's close by.
里面更棒
Wait till you see the inside.
四间精美的卧室
Four proper bedrooms...
而且衣柜的空间超多
and the place is just swimming in closet space.
其实我们没有很想要大衣柜
That's not really high on our wish list.
我们之前的衣柜把我吃掉了
Our last closet ate me.
你真可爱
That's sweet.
总之这间房子真的很有特色
Anyway, this house just screams character.
看看这些壁板和走廊
Look at the wainscoting. And in here is the foyer.
里里外外都有当时的风格
Period detail throughout.
这是起居室
And this is the den.
正面对着后院，很适合小孩
The den leads right into the back yard. Perfect for the kids.
看到那棵老树了吗？房子盖好前…
And do you see that tree? It's ancient. It was here before...
人呢？
Hello?
你们在哪？
好极了
Perfect.
我们快走吧
Let's get out of here.
这座如迷宫般的下水道
Is this labyrinthine network of sewers playing host...
有没有恶灵四窜呢？
to a malevolent spirit?
我是卡利根伯克，我来这是…
I'm Carrigan Burke, and I'm here to...
我是布鲁克拍威尔，我们来清理鬼屋
And I'm Brooke Powell, and we're here to clean house.
- 我还没讲完！  - 抱歉，不是该我了吗？
- I hadn't finished! - I'm sorry. Was that not my cue?
- 我还没讲完  - 对不起
- I hadn't finished my line. - I'm sorry.
我们不会说“清理鬼屋”，剪掉
And we're not saying "clean house." We cut that.
我以为“卡利根伯克”后就该我
Because I thought that my cue was when you said, "And I'm Carrigan Burke."
- 我没说  - 我听到“我来”
- I didn't even say that. - As soon as I heard "and"...
所以我就出场了
I just came right out.
但你还是错了
That's the wrong one, though.
好吧
Okay.
谁能告诉我到底怎么讲才对？
Does someone wanna tell me the right one?